[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Governor, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I'm great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Somebody tweeted me in the middle of last night's show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "How do you react to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, you know I explained.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "None of this is very good for the president, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, look, first of all, you cannot deny that there are still people out of work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Have you recovered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I'm very well, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Any regrets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "None.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "But were you surprised by the ferocity of the attacks on you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "ELCH: Particularly -- I was surprised when you think about the fact that they've called Governor Romney a felon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack", "Mitt Romney", "Jack Welch"]}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "This is 2,000 people calling up and saying, are you working?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Here's the problem I see for you, Jack, going forward is if Mitt Romney becomes president, every single time the job figure is announced and it's gone down, i.e., it's good news for him, every Democrat will jump up and say, Jack Welch says this is complete rubbish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "That is green shoot for the housing industry, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Auto is as strong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Do you want to take a chance on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Well, we did --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "If that's what gets Obama home, wasn't that one op-ed piece a disaster?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "They put it into the wrong place with the wrong headline.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Is it down to a question mark?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I -- no, hold it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Donald, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Hello, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "But what is the difference between Mitt Romney's refusal to release his tax returns and the president not being inclined to release his college records?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, there's a massive difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What's stopping him -- in this new spirit of transparency that you want to see, what is to stop your friend Mitt just saying, you know what, I know there are doubts, people still -- see the offshore records, here it is going back 12 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "RB", ":", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you, as far as I'm concerned, I think, and I told this to Mitt, if you -- if he release I'd like to do a swap.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Piers, why wouldn't he do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, the only reason he would do it --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Well, why wouldn't he take it up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, I don't think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "But Piers, why wouldn't he take it up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I don't think he would, is my point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Well, the point is it was memorable, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Memorably awful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "What do you think of Clint Eastwood and his apparent flip- flopping?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I think it's probably a rehabilitation of Clint Eastwood as much as it is an endorsement of Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clint Eastwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I don't see -- you are right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Right, you would like Mitt Romney to stand up tomorrow and say that God intends rapes to happen, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "That's not what he said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Am I wrong here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I don't think we should misquote him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Charles Blow, am I misrepresenting when he says that basically he's saying, look, you know, women who get raped and have babies, it's all God's will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Right, and I think there's a part -- this becomes very personal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Katie Pavlich, why is it not a woman's decision in the most most appalling circumstance of being raped, that she decides without any fear of censure from anybody else in America -- she decides what she does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I personally believe that there should be an exception in the case of rape.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katie Pavlich"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Goldman"]}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Are there any things that you regret about all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "What I would say is this idea that Goldman is relieved or find nothing in the book, I think this is part of this Wall Street mentality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121024pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", ":", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Do you see any changes since this has all blown up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "The biggest misconception right now in terms of the financial crisis, -- Dodd-Frank was a bill that was passed almost two years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]